[{"answer": "Honey!  Wait a minut", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Yeah, but I don't want him to see you", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You give your loyalty to a Jew over your own blood", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "He did business...but he never trusted him", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Sleeping inside me", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yes, my friend, it does", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Because he knows the", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Beautiful", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " This man informs to the polic", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " If I'm wrong, they will kill me", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I don't think so.  Unless I'm very wrong...they're already dead. Killed by someone inside...very frightened that they botched it. That's why I am going to disappear in a few minutes, and leave everything to you", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "If I'm wrong..", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "We got friends in the commission", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What about my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I want you to settle on their terms", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Trust m", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "It would be the beginning of the end for my family.  How can I keep all my other territories in like if I let two wis", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Always... But sometimes I don't understand.  I know I'll never have your kind of brains, in big deals. But my friend, this is a street thing. And my friend in that place is behind the my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "It occurred to m", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "So, that occurred to me", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Oh.  my friend, what's up?  I'm totally in the dark", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Great, that place's great.  Lots of activity in that place!  Anybody I know here.  Fiv", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What's that", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Sincere.  What are you talking about, of course I'm sincere with you, my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " He said he would have the police put us out", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "My friends are all her", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " You talk about the baby.  She can have another baby", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " Your family?  How can you ever lose your family", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "That is a complete falsehood", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "That is not true.  I own some stock in some of the hotels, but only very small amounts.  I also own some American Telephone and that place stock", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Some deal.  I just wish my friend had took the Fifth", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I didn't turn against nobod", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Mr. my friend, would you kindly identify to this committee that gentleman sitting on your right hand", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Is he related to the witness", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " Yes, sir.  His name is my friend", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "He is, I believe, a brother", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I'll bring the children up no", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Goodbye, my friend", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "He's her", "docId": "Godfather-Part-II.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Ah.  Okay, kid, you got to go to my friend with your Pop", "qsentId": 40}]